my name is Josh Johnson and I'm
originally from Louisiana growing up in
Louisiana was like being in a bathtub
and you can't get out and the water is
dirty and it's racist I'm into comic
books a lot it started out when I was
young I couldn't afford the good comics
so I would get these sort of like
discontinued publications that were like
a quarter because of that I never knew
what other kids were talking about then
I read spire mounds like this is way
better oh my gosh I wish I had grown up
with with even a little bit of money and
then I would have just bought the dollar
twenty five comic and knowing what my
friends were talking about the advice
that I wish I got when I first started
was to quit I stuck with comedy because
even though a bomb is the scary thing
that no comic wants to experience I
don't do that well in individual
conversations and so a comedy show is
just bombing with everyone at one time
you know until it went really well and
then it was like a drug I was I was
addicted to sort of making people laugh
because I grew up alone and and didn't
have a ton of friends and so whenever
I'm onstage it's like everyone's my
friend for a little while oh god that's
so sad like I did like I realize how sad
that was until I was done saying it clap
your hands everybody for just Johnson
oh how you guys doing everybody good I
don't know if you can tell by looking at
me but uh I was fired from being in a
gang they kicked me out because I was
too positive they were like why you
always smile at Dawg I'm like I mean
none of us are dead or in jail and we're
a gang they also kicked me out because I
apologize too much
our drive-bys sounded like hmm sorry
like that after a while I saw their
point Hannah and even when it came down
to it and they were kicking me out and I
was like I want I just wanna hang out my
friends and you guys are my friends and
now I don't know what I'm going to do
that what why do I have to leave and
they were like brought you giggle
[Laughter]
[Music]